<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Yinliang Diao Homepage</title>
  
  
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2021-04-26T02:08:33.399Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Y Diao</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2021/04/19/hello-world/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2021/04/19/hello-world/</id>
    <published>2021-04-19T02:03:22.360Z</published>
    <updated>2021-04-26T02:08:33.399Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<hr><h2 id="Yinliang-Diao’s-Homepage"><a href="#Yinliang-Diao’s-Homepage" class="headerlink" title="Yinliang Diao’s Homepage"></a>Yinliang Diao’s Homepage</h2><p>Research Associate professor, Nagoya Institute of Technology<br>Assistant professor, South China Agricultural University<br>Member of ICNIRP SEG<br>Member of IEEE ICES TC95</p><h2 id="Publication-List"><a href="#Publication-List" class="headerlink" title="Publication List"></a>Publication List</h2><p><strong>Journal Publications</strong></p><p>[1]   Y. Diao, and A. Hirata, “Exposure assessment of array antennas at 28 GHz using hybrid spherical near-field transformation and FDTD method,” IEEE Transactions on Electromagnetic Compatibility, 2021, DOI: 10.1109/TEMC.2021.3074658..</p><p>[2]   Y. Diao, E. A. Rashed, and A. Hirata, “Assessment of absorbed power density and temperature rise for nonplanar body model under electromagnetic exposure above 6 GHz,” Phys. Med. Biol., vol. 64. p. 224001, 2020.</p><p>[3]   T. Murakawa, Y. Diao, E. A. Rashed, S. Kodera, Y. Tanaka, Y. Kamimura, S. Kitamura, S. Uehara, Y. Otaka, A. Hirata, “Evaluation of SAR and Temperature Rise in Human Hand due to Contact Current from 100 kHz to 100 MHz,” IEEE Access, vol. 8, pp. 200995-201004, 2020.</p><p>[4]   A. Kumazawa, Y. Diao, A. Hirata, and H. Hirayama, “Reduction of Human Interaction with Wireless Power Transfer System Using Shielded Loop Coil,” Electronics, vol. 9, no. 6, p. 953, 2020.</p><p>[5]   E. A. Rashed, Y. Diao, S. Tanaka, T. Sakai, J. Gomez-Tames, and A. Hirata, “Effect of skin-to-skin contact on stimulation threshold and dosimetry,” IEEE Trans. Electromagn. Compat., pp. 1–10, 2020.</p><p>[6]   E. A. Rashed, Y. Diao, and A. Hirata, “Learning-based estimation of dielectric properties and tissue density in head models for personalized radio-frequency dosimetry,” Phys. Med. Biol., vol. 65, no. 6, p. 65001, 2020.</p><p>[7]   Y. Diao, E. A. Rashed, and A. Hirata, “Large-Scale Analysis of the Head Proximity Effects on Antenna Performance Using Machine Learning Based Models,” IEEE Access, vol. 8, pp. 154060–154071, 2020.</p><p>[8]   Y. Diao, J. Gomez-Tames, E. A. Rashed, R. Kavet, and A. Hirata, “Spatial averaging schemes of in situ electric field for low-frequency magnetic field exposures,” IEEE Access, vol. 7, pp. 184320–184331, 2019.</p><p>[9]   K. Taguchi, I. Laakso, K. Aga, A. Hirata, Y. Diao, J. Chakarothai, and T. Kashiwa, “Relationship of external field strength with local and whole-body averaged specific absorption rates in anatomical human models,” IEEE Access, vol. 6, pp. 70186–70196, 2018.</p><p>[10]   K. Aga, A. Hirata, I. Laakso, H. Tarao, Y. Diao, T. Ito, Y. Sekiba, and K. Yamazaki, “Intercomparison of in situ electric fields in human models exposed to spatially uniform magnetic fields,” IEEE Access, vol. 6, pp. 70964–70973, 2018.</p><p>[11]  Y. Diao, W. Sun, Y. He, S. W. Leung, and Y. M. Siu, “Equivalent magnetic vector potential model for low-frequency magnetic exposure assessment,” Phys. Med. Biol., vol. 62, no. 19, p. 7905, 2017.</p><p>[12]  Y. Diao, S. W. Leung, Y. He, W. Sun, K. H. Chan, Y. M. Siu, and R. Kong, “Detailed modeling of palpebral fissure and its influence on SAR and temperature rise in human eye under GHz exposures,” Bioelectromagnetics, vol. 37, no. 4, pp. 256–263, 2016.</p><p>[13]  Y. Diao, S.-W. Leung, K. H. Chan, W. Sun, Y.-M. Siu, and R. Kong, “The effect of gaze angle on the evaluations of sar and temperature rise in human eye under plane-wave exposures from 0.9 to 10 GHz,” Radiat. Prot. Dosimetry., vol. 172, no. 4, pp. 393-400, 2016.</p><p>[14]  Y. Diao, W. Sun, S. W. Leung, K. H. Chan, and Y. M. Siu, “Prediction of magnetic field emissions by current source reconstruction using radial basis function network,” Electron. Lett., vol. 51, no. 16, pp. 1243–1245, 2015.</p><p>[15]  Y. Wu, W. Sun, S.-W. Leung, Y. Diao, and K.-H. Chan, “A compact microstrip wideband arbitrary branch-line coupler with coupled-line impedance-transforming structures,” Electromagnetics, vol. 33, no. 3, pp. 256–270, 2013.</p><p>[16]  Y. Wu, W. Sun, S.-W. P. Leung, Y. Diao, and K.-H. Chan, “A novel compact dual-frequency coupled-line transformer with simple analytical design equations for frequency-dependent complex load impedance,” Prog. Electromagn. Res., vol. 134, pp. 47–62, 2013.</p><p>[17]  Y. Wu, W. Sun, S.-W. Leung, Y. Diao, K.-H. Chan, and Y.-M. Siu, “Single-Layer Microstrip High-Directivity Coupled-Line Coupler With Tight Coupling,” IEEE Trans. Microw. Theory Tech. , vol. 61, no. 2, pp. 746–753, 2013.</p><p>[18]  S.-W. Leung, Y. Diao, K.-H. Chan, Y.-M. Siu, and Y. Wu, “Specific Absorption Rate Evaluation for Passengers Using Wireless Communication Devices Inside Vehicles With Different Handedness, Passenger Counts, and Seating Locations,” IEEE Trans. Biomed. Eng., vol. 59, no. 10, pp. 2905–2912, 2012.</p><p><strong>Conference Publications</strong><br>[1]   Y. Diao, A. Hirata, “Comparison of spatial averaging methods of in situ electric field for low-Frequency magnetic field exposures,” in XXXIII General Assembly and Scientific Symposium (GASS) of the International Union of Radio Science, Rome, 2020.<br>[2]   Z. Feng, Y. Diao, W. Sun, Y. He, and S. W. Leung, “Human exposure to wireless charging systems for electric vehicles in multistorey carpark,” in 2019 Joint International Symposium of Electromagnetic Compatibility, Sapporo and Asia-Pacific International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility (EMC Sapporo/APEMC), Sapporo, 2019, pp. 48–51.<br>[3]   Y. He, P. S. W. Leung, Y. Chow, and Y. Diao, “Dosimetry Analysis of A 3-D Open-Structured Wireless Power Transfer System,” in 2019 Joint International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility, Sapporo and Asia-Pacific International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility (EMC Sapporo/APEMC)}, Sapporo, 2019, pp. 750–753.<br>[4]   Z. Feng, Y. Diao, and X. Deng, “Phase Noise Suppression for Antenna Near-Field Measurement at Submillimeter Wave Band,” in 2019 International Conference on Microwave and Millimeter Wave Technology (ICMMT), Guangzhou, 2019, pp. 1–3.<br>[5]   Y. Diao, M. Z. Li, W. Sun, S. W. Leung, Y. X. Cai, F. Zhu, and Y. Yang, “Safety consideration for emerging wireless technologies-evaluations of temperature rise in eyes for RF radiations up to 10 GHz,” in 2018 12th International Symposium on Medical Information and Communication Technology (ISMICT), Sydney, 2018, pp. 1–3.<br>[6]   W. Sun, Y. He, Y. Diao, S. Leung, Y. Siu, and Y. Kong, “Parametric study of impact of static magnetic field on human cell viability,” in 2018 IEEE International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility and 2018 IEEE Asia-Pacific Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility (EMC/APEMC), Singapore, 2018, pp. 872–874.<br>[7]   R. B. V. B. Simorangkir, Y. Yang, K. P. Esselle, and Y. Diao, “A varactor-tuned frequency-reconfigurable fabric antenna embedded in polymer: Assessment of suitability for wearable applications,” In 2017 IEEE MTT-S International Microwave Symposium (IMS), Honolulu, 2017, pp. 204–207.<br>[8]   W. Sun, Y. He, Y. Diao, S. W. Leung, Y. M. Siu, R. Y. C. Kong, W. K. Lo, “A 3D coil structure achieving uniform magnetic field for in-vitro cell experiments,” in 2017 International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility - EMC EUROPE, Angers, 2017, pp. 1–4.<br>[9]   W. Sun, Y. He, Y. Diao, S. W. Leung, Y. M. Siu, and R. Y. C. Kong, “Impact of magnetic field generated by wireless power transfer system of electric vehicle on retinal pigment epithelium cell in vitro,” in 2017 Asia-Pacific International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility (APEMC), Seoul, 2017, pp. 385–387.<br>[10]  Y. Diao, W. Sun, S. W. Leung, Y. M. Siu, and K. H. Chan, “Equivalent current model for assessing human exposure to inhomogeneous LF magnetic fields,” In 7th Asia-Pacific International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility &amp; Signal Integrity and Technical Exhibition, Shenzhen, 2016, vol. 1, pp. 329–331.<br>[11]  Y. He, Y. Diao, W. Sun, S. W. Leung, and Y. M. Siu, “Impact of magnetic-field generated by wireless power transfer of electric vehicles on brain waves and neuro-psychological changes,” in 7th Asia-Pacific International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility &amp; Signal Integrity and Technical Exhibition, Shenzhen, 2016, vol. 1, pp. 639–641.<br>[12]  Y. He, S. W. Leung, Y. Diao, W. Sun, Y. M. Siu, P. Sinha, K. H. Chan, “Impacts of radio frequency interference on human brain waves and neuro-psychological changes,” In 2015 International Conference on Intelligent Informatics and Biomedical Sciences (ICIIBMS), Okinawa, 2015, pp. 257–261.<br>[13]  Y. Diao, W. Sun, S. W. Leung, Y. M. Siu, and K. H. Chan, “Prediction of magnetic field radiation using equivalent current distribution,” In Joint IEEE International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility and EMC Europe, Dresden, Aug 2015, pp. 887-890.<br>[14]  Y. Diao, W. Sun, K. H. Chan, S. W. Leung, and Y. M. Siu, “Study of effects of commercial shielding products attached to mobile phone on human body with implanted medical device,” in 2014 International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility, Tokyo (EMC14/Tokyo), 2014, pp. 226–229.<br>[15]  Y. Diao, W. Sun, K. H. Chan, S. W. Leung, and Y. M. Siu, “SAR evaluation for multiple wireless communication devices inside a vehicle,” in Proceedings of 2013 URSI International Symposium on Electromagnetic Theory (EMTS), Hiroshima, 2013, pp. 626–629.<br>[16]  K. H. Chan, Y. Diao, S. W. Leung, W. Sun, and Y. M. Siu, “Study of power frequency radiation to axis-symmetric human model implanted with pacemaker,” in 2012 International Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility (EMC EUROPE), Rome, 2012, pp. 1–6.<br>[17]  K. H. Chan, S. W. Leung, Y. Diao, Y. M. Siu, and K. T. Ng, “Analysis of millimeter wave radiation to human body using inhomogeneous multilayer skin model,” in 2012 Asia-Pacific Symposium on Electromagnetic Compatibility (APEMC), Singapore, 2012, pp. 721–724.<br>[18]  Y. Diao, Y. M. Shen, and Y. G. Gao, “Design of coil structure achieving uniform magnetic field distribution for wireless charging platform,” in 4th International Conference on Power Electronics Systems and Applications (PESA), Hong Kong, 2011, pp. 1–5.</p><h2 id="Researches"><a href="#Researches" class="headerlink" title="Researches"></a>Researches</h2><h4 id="Bioeletromagnetic-simulation"><a href="#Bioeletromagnetic-simulation" class="headerlink" title="Bioeletromagnetic simulation"></a>Bioeletromagnetic simulation</h4><img src="https://i.loli.net/2021/04/19/xWAIq45UQmN9oDd.png" alt="FDTD" style="zoom:36%;" /><img src="https://i.loli.net/2021/04/19/MDZtHs6yLmOFKwc.png" alt="FieldHead" style="zoom:36%;" /><img src="https://i.loli.net/2021/04/19/ujgKwvrYz8QdIBS.png" alt="Patterns" style="zoom:36%;" /><img src="https://i.loli.net/2021/04/19/u2a35hjWvcXyYKU.png" alt="ExposAsses" style="zoom:36%;" /><h4 id="Antenna-near-field-measurement-and-NFFF-algorithm"><a href="#Antenna-near-field-measurement-and-NFFF-algorithm" class="headerlink" title="Antenna near-field measurement and NFFF algorithm"></a>Antenna near-field measurement and NFFF algorithm</h4><img src="https://i.loli.net/2021/04/19/dt1CfJRM8GFsqvc.png" alt="Spherical1" style="zoom:36%;" /><img src="https://i.loli.net/2021/04/19/sMzXwqinUcTCZj3.png" alt="Spherical2" style="zoom:36%;" /><h3 id=""><a href="#" class="headerlink" title=""></a></h3><h3 id="-1"><a href="#-1" class="headerlink" title=""></a></h3>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;Yinliang-Diao’s-Homepage&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Yinliang-Diao’s-Homepage&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Yinliang Diao’s Homepage&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Yinliang </summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
